<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brennan Macaig</title>
    <link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brennan Macaig</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 12:29:25 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brennanmacaig.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code - What, why, when, how?</title>
      <link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/posts/advent-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 12:29:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/posts/advent-intro/</guid>
      <description>As the holiday season begins with the end of black friday (and the winding down of my semester) - a new but familiar challenge approaches. I am of course talking about Advent of Code - the crazy series of events put together by Eric Wastl.
Every year, I do (at least part of) the Advent of Code (or AoC) challenges. And every year, I progress further in the set of challenges than I did the year before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi, I&#39;m Brennan.</title>
      <link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 12:09:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Site Reliability Engineering Intern at Mutualink, a full time CS student at UMass Lowell, and a FIRST robotics mentor. I&amp;rsquo;m currently based out of Lowell MA (greater Boston area).
As a site reliability engineer, I focus on building secure, scalable, maintainable infrastructure. Previously, I worked as a full stack web developer, writing performance-oriented business-to-business SaaS apps.
In my free time, I maintain a blog, as well as develop personal IoT projects around the house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking to reach me?</title>
      <link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 12:09:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can always email me at my personal email: me@brennanmacaig.com (I check this daily).
You could also @ me on my Twitter, or message me on my GitHub.
Further, you could try reaching me on LinkedIn.
 There&amp;rsquo;s a problem with your website    I&amp;rsquo;m sorry about that! Feel free to reach out to me via either my personal email or help@brennanmacaig.com. I&amp;rsquo;ll fix it right away!
I think you copied my content without permission    I certainly hope not!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howdy!</title>
      <link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 12:07:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>My name is Brennan, and welcome to my new blog.
I&amp;rsquo;m trying to be more active in writing a blog - this will be mostly useless musings, with maybe the occasional interesting story.
A lot of what I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing will be something along the lines of &amp;ldquo;today I learned&amp;rdquo; - as I am very much still a student (oh hey, thanks Blake for this fantastic idea).
Recently, a friend of mine Nate started a new blog, which really inspired me to get on the blog writing train.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
